<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content"><channel><title>EDGAR SGROI</title><description>Welcome to my personal website!</description><link>https://your-website-url.com</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 15:41:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 15:41:15 +0000</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="https://your-website-url.com/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://your-website-url.com/myprojects/blink</guid><title>Blink! - Brainstorming</title><description>A SwiftUI app made for brainstorming using an Apple TV and multiple iPhones.</description><link>https://your-website-url.com/myprojects/blink</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 15:38:59 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Blink! - Brainstorming</h1><div class="icon-description">
    <div>
        <img class="icon" src="https://your-website-url.com/images/blink/logos/BlinkiOSIcon.png" alt="Blink Icon"/>
    </div>
    <div style="margin-left: 20px;">
        Brainstorming is a idea creation and problem resolution process commonly used in the through out the entire world. With "Blink!" you will be able to connect simultaneously with up to 7 iPhones, send ideas through your connected within the timelimit, conduct voting sessions and check out the final ranking of the most voted ideas.
        <br/>
        Blink! on iOS is a companion app for the Apple TV app of the same name. It can't be used alone.
        <br/><br/>
        <h4> GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/csfar/blink">https://github.com/csfar/blink</a> </h4>
        <h4> AppStore: <a href="https://apps.apple.com/br/app/blink-brainstorming/id1524089387">https://apps.apple.com/br/app/blink-brainstorming/id1524089387</a> </h4>
    </div>
</div><br/><br/><h3>About</h3><br/><div>
Blink! is a tvOS app with a iOS companion, both developed using SwiftUI. In addition to the design, I developed all the communication between iOS and tvOS, using Multipeer Connectivity. With Blink! is possible to realize group brainstorming sessions on a AppleTV using iPhones to interaction.
</div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://your-website-url.com/myprojects/formworks</guid><title>Formworks</title><description>Formworks is a framework for building forms from JSON files.</description><link>https://your-website-url.com/myprojects/formworks</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 15:38:59 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Formworks</h1><div class="icon-description">
    <div>
        <img class="icon" src="https://your-website-url.com/images/formworks/logos/FormworksShortLogo.png" alt="Formworks Logo"/>
    </div>
    <div style="margin-left: 20px;">
        Formworks is a framework for building forms from JSON files using Server Driven UI pattern.
        <br/><br/>
        <h4> GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/MyFormworks/Formworks">https://github.com/MyFormworks/Formworks</a> </h4>
    </div>
</div><br/><br/><h3>About</h3><br/><p>Formworks is a Open-Source framework licensed under the MIT license develped to facilitate the creation of forms on iOS aplications. Inspired by Server-driven UI, Formworks works using JSONs that describe all the components and characteristics of the form and set validation rules for each component using Regex. Formworks aims to be the simplest way to build usable forms.</p><p>I develped many parts of the framework, such as some parts of the UI, Components Validators, documentation, I also integrated the CI and Jazzy Action.<br><div>

</div></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://your-website-url.com/myprojects/goals</guid><title>Goals</title><description>Create objectives, set goals and track your progress with Goals app.</description><link>https://your-website-url.com/myprojects/goals</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 15:38:59 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Goals</h1><div class="icon-description">
    <div>
        <img class="icon" src="https://your-website-url.com/images/goals/logos/GoalsLogo.png" alt="Goals Icon"/>
    </div>
    <div style="margin-left: 20px;">
        Goals uses methodologies and good practices as a foundation to help control and manage your goals. Define them create strategies that best adapt to your lifestyle by managing your progress and measuring your evolution.
        <br/><br/>
        <h4> GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/EdgSgroi/GoalsApp">https://github.com/EdgSgroi/GoalsApp</a> </h4>
        <h4> AppStore: <a href="https://apps.apple.com/br/app/goals/id1474726284#?platform=ipad">https://apps.apple.com/br/app/goals/id1474726284#?platform=ipad</a> </h4>
    </div>
</div><br/><br/><h3>About</h3><br/><div>
Goals is a productivity app. It focus on manege your personal objectives dividing them into smal goals that, when completed, them take you a little closer to the first. It was developed using MVC architecture but refactored to MVVM-C pattern latter. Also using Storyboard and Core Data, Goals is the first app that I developed and disigned complety alone. It is in constant updating.
</div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://your-website-url.com/myprojects/projeta</guid><title>Projeta</title><description>Projeta is an application for those looking to advertise or join academic projects throughout Brazil.</description><link>https://your-website-url.com/myprojects/projeta</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 15:38:59 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Projeta</h1><div class="icon-description">
    <div>
        <img class="icon" src="https://your-website-url.com/images/projeta/logos/ProjetaIcon.png" alt="Projeta Icon"/>
    </div>
    <div style="margin-left: 20px;">
        Projeta is an application for those looking to advertise or join academic projects throughout Brazil. With it you can create or ask to participate in projects that are of interest to you, as there are five types of categories supported. It is possible to easily view those projects in which you participate and manage your own projects, updating the requests for participation and the stage in which they are.
        <br/><br/>
        <h4> GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/paulaleite/remoteMiniChallenge3">https://github.com/paulaleite/remoteMiniChallenge3</a> </h4>
        <h4> AppStore: <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/projeta/id1518661950">https://apps.apple.com/us/app/projeta/id1518661950</a> </h4>
    </div>
</div><br/><br/><h3>About</h3><br/><div>
Projeta is a projects platafom that studants and teachers can publicize their projects in reason to find people interested to participate. I developed the iOS back-end and server back-end. it is a app that works only in the Brazil and is in constant develpment.
</div>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>